But why are we here, too?
We volunteered to come in for questioning.
We didn't break any laws.
The little blonde one over there.
Audrey's her name, isn't it?
Hmm?
She managed to launch some kind of
intense psychological attack on my mind,
didn't she?
No, that's not true!
I mean, it's just...
In this case,
it's more of a curse that makes
everyone in her vicinity act like this.
It's a type of charm, then, is it?
Ah, I see.
Psychological attacks
don't tend to work on me
because I've trained a
long time to prevent that.
Nevertheless,
it's impossible to ignore that my general
awareness of you has
been greatly enhanced.
Would you care for a piece of candy?
Ooh, you're sharing?
Of course!
Stop kidding yourself.
Though unintentional,
I cannot turn a blind eye to a
psychological attack on my person.
If you help me with this, then just
like that, you'll be declared innocent.
Please try to think of it
as a simple assistance.
You're strong, aren't you?
I mean, you did defeat this, after all.
You've been calling me this and that.
Could you maybe use my name instead?
It is a little hard to
remember such a long name.
Let's give you a nickname, huh?
How would you feel about Schwarzie?
We've only just met, but we're
close enough to use nicknames.
Could it be that she feels...
Anyway, setting aside
this unimportant matter...
Hey, it is not unimportant!
I should give you another
overview of what we're doing here.
Recently,
along the roads in town,
a suit of living armor is reported
to have been robbing people.
We deployed a suppression team, but...
They were unfortunately found
stripped of all their belongings.
They were stripped of their belongings?
Apparently every single
one of them was naked
Suddenly I have a bad feeling about this
still though there haven't
been any fatalities.
I don't think there's much danger, but
Is that our target?
I believe so.
Magic.
I've some strong magical power.
Leave it here. It's huge. Right.
Looks like it's my turn to step up.
Wait.
Are you really planning to use
that sword in a place like this?
The forest will be completely laid bare.
And if anyone's here foraging for
edible plants, they'll be cut in two.
I understand, father.
It's too soon to be lured in by the
sword's surging destructive power.
You're saying that men should use their own
natural abilities in a challenge, right?
I am not.
And up till this moment, I've always
fought with this sword still sheathed.
So now let's go, Gram!
He's fast.
Even compared to the knights of our
land, his technique is excellent, but...
Hey, stand back! It's coming!
Wait! Wait!
That was actually pretty good!
No! No!
My crap!
Living armor requires
magic in order to move.
It was obviously after
the magic and the sword.
But it speaks human language.
Living armor is a magic weapon
that can move autonomously.
I've never heard of one with a
mechanism to have a person inside.
What is this thing?
Audrey, go!
You have to run now!
It's after that tiara!
Wow, thanks!
You saved my butt! Of course.
I hate to lose the ability to walk
around freely, but I have to ditch this.
You, interrogator.
I wonder if you'd tell
me your annual income.
My annual income? Yes.
I'm afraid it's of the utmost importance.
I don't think there's a need
to go into my personal...
Please tell me!
My salary is 100 gold coins annually.
What of it?
You understand now, don't you, Audrey?
As shocking as this may be on your
head, you're wearing three years' worth!
of a government worker's salary!
It's worth three years of their salary?!
For a working adult, the tuna
freeze has a very harsh ring to it.
Jinko Jinko, defeat that thing!
That's a surprisingly
backhanded way to raise morale.
Just starting around.
You're wide open!
How was that?
I used enough strength
to pierce through steel.
It may be living armor,
but it won't be unscathed.
Dude, you okay?
This armor is made of magical
steel, forged using ancient methods.
It's magical power from the
outside is absorbed or deflected,
and it automatically repairs itself.
So you're saying you're an ancient weapon?
That's right.
Be afraid, human children.
I am Viz the incomparably skilled, one of
the top officers of the Demon Lord's army.
One of their top officers?
Incomparably skilled?
Vizzd, is it?
Wait, but how can this be?
It can't be true.
It couldn't be.
That's not...
The terror I see in your
eyes is truly gratifying.
I didn't know!
Dude, are you actually a lady?
Sorry for assuming you
were a guy until now.
Yeah, don't worry.
I know it's the way I choose
to carry myself after all.
Drape this over you for now.
Thank you for that.
Everyone withdraw.
I'm prepared to act as a decoy. You sure?
I'll be fine.
I believe its only goal
is to amass magic power.
Worst case scenario, I'll be naked. What?
That's not fine at all!
Hey, can't you do something
about this, Jango G?
At this rate, the interrogator
will end up naked!
Mary!
Please! Just...
Please marry me, my beautiful Audrey!
What the heck are you guys doing?
I want to save the world for you!
I don't know what children!
Wait, no, it's...
Why does it feel like everyone's under
some kind of curse to say that to me?
Never mind!
Just put that on!
And sit over there!
I can't withstand it feels like
my mind was about to break!
Honestly...
Here!
Is this good enough?
I'm sitting off to the side
and I'm not showing any skin!
So now could you do the thing, please?
The jacket's on, just like I instructed.
But this Tachibana is...
how can I put it?
I can't seem to calm myself.
I feel sort of floaty and fluffy.
What is this feeling?
Why are you worse now?
I got dressed, jeez!
I don't know! Why is that?
Watanabe, I know why.
Just look at her.
Schwarzie?
You dare to ignore me?
Sorry, Armoredude, just a sec.
That profound feeling you're experiencing
right now actually has a name.
It's known as the Boyfriend Shirt.
Did he say Boyfriend Shirt?
The Boyfriend Shirt.
When a girlfriend goes to
stay at her boyfriend's house,
in the case that no other
sleepwear is available,
it may be possible to catch
her in this very rare state.
Since the clothes are oversized, it
looks like she isn't wearing any bottoms.
Mind-blowing,
and the thought that she's
enveloped in your scent
is also considered to be
the awesomest of awesome
It is one of the top three
imaginings of the virgin male
Jinguuji, you're as pure as freshly
fallen snow aren't you? Yeah,
that's the kind of thing a
high schooler would squeal
over Don't make up lies about
other people's preferences.
Well, it's just that it looks like
you've already committed to it
This thing is really a nuisance
You make a mockery of me.
If you would prefer for me to hunt you
down, then I shall do exactly that!
A boyfriend's shirt.
What a ridiculous idea.
No interest!
The fact that anyone assumes I'm a man who
would be swayed by such
a thing is abominable!
Rectify this, Tazibana!
Look, Jiggity! Behind you! Behind you!
Don't change the subject!
It's being said that I'm a man of
childish taste and that really irks me!
That's fine.
But seriously, though,
are you gonna be okay?
And besides,
compared to your interest
in funny girls and maids,
I happen to think my tastes are a
little more in the realm of normal!
Oh, so it's okay for you to
mock someone's preferences?
Stop this endless darting around!
You shouldn't knock it
before you try it, Chinguji.
Why don't you imagine it
with me as your model?
Imagine what?
Isn't it obvious?
A bunny girl, of course.
A bunny. A bunny?
You're MINE!
That won't work on me!
So what about bunny girls?
You think something so simple
will make my heart dance?
Simple, huh?
How about a maid uniform, then?
How's that?
A maid uniform.
Oh, I bet you'd like the
type with long skirts.
If a direct hit and a blow
from my axe are ineffective,
then absorb magical power
and focus into boosters.
Reinforce joints and
increase physical strength.
Full sec mode!
It's a long-skirted maid uniform look
like all right there it is no effect
THIS IS BAD!
What's with the whole welcome
home master thing anyway?
It's ridiculous to think
that one would automatically
call someone they've only just met master!
Shut up!
Why are you always so condescending to me?
That's a really annoying habit!
Bad habit or not, it's true!
Anyway, it's your fault for doing
such stupid things all the time!
It's not to shut up!
You shut up!
A girl?
My, my, kun!
Mm-mm-mm-mm-mm.
And all this time, I thought the
Demon Lord was just a story for kids.
Then you show up here saying you've brought
in one of the Demon Lord's top officers.
I actually find this turn of events
difficult to believe as well.
Yeah, well, don't let it
get to your heads, human!
You're gonna get beat into a bloody pulp
when my comrades come and rescue me,
and that will be the end of you!
That's big talk from somebody who's
hogtied and waiting to be rescued.
Do you actually have comrades?
Give me the numbers, how many do you...
You're quite the lively one,
Vizzd, the incomparably skilled.
Okay, that tingled a little bit.
I haven't forgotten what you did.
I bear a grudge for my ripped clothes.
Her face is scary, and I am afraid.
She is an interrogator.
Blast it!
If I weren't in this form, you wouldn't
even be drawing breath right now!
She's crying.
What a pathetic sight.
Hey, you!
Where is this demon lord or whatever?
If you're a top officer, you
must at least know where he is.
You want to know where the demon lord is?
I see, so you lot haven't even
realized the truth yet, have you?
Well, that's certainly convenient for me.
I'll have to make sure and gather
more magic before the hero appears.
If you're saying that you believe that a
hero has not yet appeared in this world,
then you are sorely mistaken, Vizd. What?
Because I am here. It's me.
I, Schwarz von
Liechtenstein-Lohengrom, am he,
the hero who has been
summoned here to battle you!
Huh?
There's no freaking way a person
as boring as you could be the hero.
WHY WON'T ANYONE IN
THIS WORLD BELIEVE ME?!
Even if you know it's a lie,
willingly giving the opposition
information is the lowest of the low.
Even my allies hate me!
Everyone please get out!
There's too much of a racket!
You're interfering with my work!
Wait, don't!
So, whatcha think's going on in there?
Dang it, putting me
through all that torment.
The core of my body is still
buzzing and tingling like crazy.
Not one blow.
I couldn't land even one blow.
I have to hurry up and get out of here so
I can start gathering more magical power.
But I don't see a way out of this mess.
Imprisoned in a sad little cell.
This is pathetic, you know.
Viz the weakest.
Oh, hello, Calm.
I doubt the Demon Lord will be inclined
to overlook this blunder. Wait, no!
What are you saying?!
I'm sure that I'll be praised by
the Demon Lord for trying so hard!
Plus, I've gotten my hands
on some good information!
The hero has already come to our world!
Ah!
Yes, I heard that from the
shadows, but I'm sure he's a fake.
He seems like a background character.
Why you little!
If you were there, you
should have rescued me early?
That stupid four-eyed jerk once
my magic has fully recovered.
I will exact my revenge for
what he's done to my armor
Really?
So the one of the glasses did this.
You better believe the next time we do
battle, I'm a thousand percent going to win.
You'll see?
Yes, yes, please don't have
a tantrum right in my ear.
I'M NOT HAVING A TANTRUM!
A VERY GOOD MORNING TO
YOU, BEAUTIFUL AUDREY!
Oh dear, could it be that you're
still wearing your nightclothes?
I mean,
I can't really conceal the fact that it
was one of my goals to see that, but...
As you are still here in your room,
I wondered if we might go
have our breakfast together!
And since I had that thought, I...
Good morning.
Oh, uh, hello there, Father. Good morning.
What is this doing here? A door?
Hello?
Uh, hello, it's Schwarz.
I got my hands full right
now, but come on in!
Hmm.
Ouch!
Yes, well, this is the ability I
received from that crappy goddess.
this
So that means this is your house Watanabe.
I thought it would be more that you would
live sort of like steeped in darkness
But this is pretty boring Well, I'm
sorry. It's so disappointing. Wait.
This is your house Audrey. Yep.
All mine That's interesting
cuz there are things
that make it feel a bit
more like a man lives here
Schwartz, you should brace yourself,
or I think the time has come for me to
tell you an incredibly painful truth.
Good morning.
Ah, did you both sleep well last night?
Yes, we'd like to thank
you for everything.
My first love!
It was my first love, and yet, Hinata
Tachibana is a 32-year-old office worker.
Also a dude.
To think I've stolen a
young man's first love.
I really am a wicked, wicked woman.
How old are you anyway, Schwarzie?
Is it written down
somewhere in your stats?
I'm a senior in high school.
And what exactly do you mean by stats?
She got away, then.
I'm very ashamed.
Though, with this method of escape, I don't
know how it could have been prevented.
And we've learned no more
about the Demon Lord.
If she were capable of something
like this she would have done it
earlier i think we should Assume
an ally came to help her i thought
we'd be able to gather information
in a large town like This i don't
see how anyone the only thing
we've seen to learn is that no one
knows anything and it Seems that
the demon lord is known here only
through folk tales would it be best
to travel To an even larger town
to investigate hey tachibana i had
no idea this existed it's handy
because you You can see the strength
of the opponent you're fighting.
Tachibana, you're basically cannon fodder.
You got that right.
All I got going for me is how cute I am.
So protect me, okay?
Just as good at making
friends as ever, I see.
This guy doesn't put up
any psychological walls.
I could never live that way.
Always surrounded by people.
And so...
Jingo G, you're too fast.
We can't catch you.
Let's just leave them.
I've remembered all the way
back to something unpleasant.
Hey, Jingo G, Schwartz says we
can look at his stats if we wanna.
Why are you hiding your name like that?
Because it's physically unbearable.
What do you mean, physically unbearable?
Listen, my name is Schwarz von Liechtenstein,
Lohengramm. Understand? That's it.
That's all.
I mean, I honestly don't care
that much, so whatever you want.
But, Schwarzie, your
level is kind of basic.
No, it's that Jinkoji's
level is way too high.
Don't mind that.
What's important are your skills.
Just look at the skills list.
Seriously, you have a ton. It's wild.
You were on the ping-pong team, huh?
Wait, that kind of info's on there, too?
Did you not know about these?
I wasn't aware of most of them.
I do know that whoever made up these
names has good taste though later.
We should test them somewhere
without people around good call.
Does that sound good to you Schwartzy?
Okay, what the heck skill
did you use to do that?
Kami mo kato li sto.
La-ku-e-n-o-to!
Ah chi-ko-no!
Kii to koo-ji-dai-yo.
Bok-ke-ka.
Let's go!
Let's see! Yeay!
Fabulous, Fabulous Totsu jo, Shutsu,
Who are you?
To ki-mi-to ki-mi-to
You go Kami-no centrist
Rakuen-no ko-pi-la-ki-la-ke Ah,
chika-na Choko chika Ki-tokou-chi-da
-yo Ai-hen-da
Deki-nai-wake-jajanai-go Dekil-wake
-Demon Suki-tekodoh-sanai-go
Kira-i-toké-jajanai
Koi-shita-wake-jajanai-go
Ai-ganai-wa-ke-jajanai Phanta-sita,
ki-mi-to ki-mi-to
Uncomparably skilled do not think
you can make me yield through pain.
Hold on.
What's that fluffy thing?
I like your voice when
you cry out like that